ANDREJ JOVANOVIĆ

WEB AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+381 69 163 8490



andrej.business@outlook.com



github.com/Dualxyz

linkedin.com/in/andrejjovanovic

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- C#
- .NET 6/7/8
- .NET Entity Framework
- Javascript / Typescript
- ReactJS / NextJS
- Python
- SQL / SQLServer
- Git/Github
- · Selenium / Playwright testing

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication
- Problem solving
- Critical thinking
- Attention to detail
- Multitasking

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Serbian Native

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Developer with over two years of professional experience. Additionally, I am currently pursuing a degree in the Faculty of Technical Science in Novi Sad, Serbia. My expertise primarily lies in .NET API development. However, I also dwelled a decent amount into Python and JavaScript frameworks. Beyond my professional commitments, I am passionate about engaging in programming projects during my spare time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack Engineer | Circular1health 2021 – 2022

I initially contributed to the front-end team and subsequently transitioned to a role within the back-end team. During my tenure, I played a pivotal role in the development of a web portal designed to streamline the process of providing airlines with access to passengers' COVID-19 status information, thereby facilitating a more efficient and effective service.

- Created forms in NextJS from a given design with a responsive and mobile-first approach.
- Ensured the stability of the web application's functionality and API through browser automation testing.
- Assisted with writing model configurations on backend for writing to database as well as refactoring code to fit more with MediatR and CQRS pattern.

Technologies used: C#, .NET 6.0, NextJS, Selenium, Playwright, HTML5, CSS3, SQLServer, SQL, GIT, Postman

Software Engineer | Freelancing 2019 – 2020

Collaborated within an international team consisting of two software engineers and one graphic designer. Our primary responsibilities encompassed designing and creating a desktop application which allowed for serializing data from a given excel file and generating a PDF based on it as well as sending SMS and email reports.

Demo: https://youtu.be/hxWRoSQfzQ0

Technologies used: Python, Pandas, PyQT Designer, GIT, Flask

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION

Faculty of Technical Science | 2020 - 2024 (estimated)

• Applied Technical Science | Informatics course

Certified Lead Auditor | 2023

• ISO/IEC 27001:2022 Lead (external) Auditor